https://www.winsite.com/help/privacy.html

WinSitespecialty archive
AudioBusinessDesktopDevelopmentGamesHome & EducationInternetMultimediaUtilitiesWeb Development
WinSite's Privacy policy
WinSite is concerned about your privacy. As with most industry-standard web serving software, each visit to our website generates a logfile entry that indicates time of visit, the domain name of your machine (e.g., "dial-54.somewhere.com") and the file(s) (and their sizes, in bytes) that your visit generated.
WinSite uses information generated from each visitor to our website to determine popular downloads and the most often-used sections of our website. WinSite does not collect personal information. We use industry standard web server logfiles to record baseline visitor information. WinSite does not sell, trade, or rent any visitor information. The data we collect is for internal use only and for the use of reporting to our advertisers the number of advertising impressions we deliver.
Cookies. We use cookies to help us learn what is important on our website.
Additionally, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this industry-standard information by WinSite Group, Inc. If changes are made to this privacy policy, they will be posted here, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Security. Any and all information that WinSite collects on its visitors is securely stored and is removed from the system each month to off-disk storage. We use additional security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Shell to access our servers remotely, and all server sessions are encrypted.
Written Correspondence. As one of the busiest and most popular sites on the Internet, we open ourselves to
the nefarious exploits of some of the more unscrupulous activities of spammers, bulk and mass e-mailers, and their ilk.
We have taken great measures to secure our file servers from their constant attack(s)
that try to use our precious resources to relay thousands of unsolicited e-mail
messages. We aggressively use the MAPS Relay Spam Stopper. WinSite does not sell mail service(s). We don't sell Internet access. We do
not send mass e-mail. We do not "do" spam. In fact, we loathe spam and those who generate it. You have our word that
you will never receive unsolicited e-mail from us. Ever. If you hate spam as much as we do, and want to learn more about spam
and how to deal with it, please visit the wonderful anti-spam web site at http://spam.abuse.net. You'll
find everything there that you need to put an end to spam once and for all!
We provide this statement as an assurance to you. We want you to know that your privacy is respected and will not be abused
or violated by visiting our site. We also hope that by providing this privacy statement, other sites will join us in reaffirming
your rights of privacy while using the Internet. Please let us know what you think about our privacy statement. Your comments are always welcome at our Contact
Page
Copyright © 1995 - 2018 WinSite.com
Home
Search WinSite
Browse WinSite
HotFiles@WinSite
Submit at WinSite
